# **Moses Ricks**

#### Rail work

Tukwila, WA mosesricks3@gmail.com - (206)496-4836

I am a self-motivated heavy equipment and machine operator with over 10 years of warehouse experience. I exemplify attention to detail, proficient in operating under tight schedules with minimal oversight, manage multiple tasks at any given time and still complete daily assignments within the shift. I'm very safety conscious.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Forklift Operator**

Genie Industries - Redmond, WA -

August 2018 to Present

Unload freight separate freight and put away

## Laborer/Operator

J&C CONSTRUCTION - Soperton, GA -

November 2016 to July 2018

Was a laborer and. Drove equipment around construction site moving material

#### **Railroad Conductor**

NWRI - Vancouver, WA -

March 2016 to March 2016

-09/2016

- Educated on the importance of safe work practices
- Railroad operations and safety rules
- Yard switching operations
- Air brake and train handling rules
- Freight car and locomotive daily inspections
- · Hazardous Materials: practices and handling
- Railroad field operations
- GCOR 7th edition
- OSHA-1910 general industry

#### Forklift Operator (Wide Format Lead)

Athens Paper - Norcross, GA -

#### September 2014 to March 2016

- Replenishments/Freight
- Pull orders
- Load trucks

## **Forklift Operator**

ProLogistix - Covington, GA -

October 2013 to August 2014

- Replenishments/Freight
- Created Bill of Ladings
- Pull orders
- Load trucks
- Experienced on MAX
- Experienced on Red Prairie

#### **EDUCATION**

#### technical diploma in railroad operations

Northwest railroad institute - Vancouver, WA

2016 to 2016

**SKILLS** 

GCOR, ABTH, (Less than 1 year)

**AWARDS** 

# safety awards

July 2014

An award for being safe and operating safe it a crowded environment

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

i have yet to miss any days of work and work on holidays if needed